PENNY:
So how do you feel?
(Penny:)Nice and loose? Come to play?
Got your game face on?
(Penny:)- Are you ready?
ALL: Oh.
Yeah. You don't have to stay
for the whole thing.
(Penny:)Oh, no, no, I want to.
Sounds really interesting.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Penny:)- Gentlemen.
- Sheldon.
(Howard:)- Sheldon.
- Hee-hee-hee.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
I'm just gonna sit down.
So is that your team?
(Sheldon:)Actually, I don't need a team.
(Sheldon:)I could easily defeat you single-handedly,
but the rules require four.
So may I introduce the third-floor janitor,
the lady from the lunch room and...
(Sheldon:)My Spanish is not good.
...either her son or her butcher.
(Sheldon:)And what about your team?
(Sheldon:)What rat have you recruited
to the S.S. Sinking Ship?
LESLIE:
Hello, Sheldon.